Smith, Bernard C.; Papers apap279
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1963-1969; Undated; 1; 9.75 cu. ft.
  - Personal, 1968-1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Personal, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Pesticides, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Pharmacist, 1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Pharmacy, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Physicians, 1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Physiotherapists, 1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Pilgrim State Hospital, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Plumbers, 1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Podiatry Bill, 1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Podiatry Practice Act, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Police File, 1967-1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Pollution Control Law, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Pornographic Material, 1966-1967 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Pornographic Material, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Power Program, 1968; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Primary, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Press Clippings, 1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Press Clippings, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Press Releases, 1968; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Principal Salary Bill, 1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Principals' Salary Bill, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Professional Engineers, 1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Professional Nurses, 1966-1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Psychology, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Public Disclosure File, 1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Public Health, Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Public Health Law, 1966-1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Public Housing, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Public Works, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Pure Waters, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Questionnaire, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Questionnaire, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Quarter Horse Racing, 1965-1967 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Racing Association, 1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Raceway, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Rain Maker, 1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Railroads, 1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Regents College Scholarships, 1966-1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Regents Scholarship Winners, 1966; 1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Rehabilitation, 1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Rehabilitation, 1969 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Rent Control, 1968 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Report: "Annual Report of the State Advisory Council on Employment and Unemployment Insurance", 1965 (Box 7 (1-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Report: "Facts About Nurses and Nursing in New York State" Office of Nurse Education, 1966 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Report: "Federal Aid and Tax Sharing", 1967 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Report: "New York State and Higher Education", 1968 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Report: "Office of Economic Opportunity Information Center, Community Profile: Suffolk County", Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Report: "Poverty and Economic Development in New York City", 1968 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Report: "Professional and Employment Characteristics of Professional Nurses Registered in New York State" SUNY, NY State Education Dept., 1966 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Report: "State of New York Dept of Public Works - In the Matter of a Hearing Held to Consider the Proposed Reconstruction of Jericho Turnpike…", Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Report: "State of New York Insurance Dept: Fees and Taxes Charged Insurance Companies.", 1968 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Report: "Tax Overlapping in the United States", 1966 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Report: "Transcript of Minutes of a Public Hearing of the Senate Finance Sub-Committee…", 1968 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Report: "The New York State Budget for 1968-69: A Review and Report." (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Report: "The Striped Bass - A Game Fish in New York State." by Frederick Schwab, 1969 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Report: "The Taylor Law", 1969 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Republic Airfield, 1968 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Republic Airport, 1969 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Requests, 1968 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Requests, 1969 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Research - Human, 1969 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Resolution 72 - Pornographic Obscene Literature, 1969 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Richard Spera, 1966 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Rodeos, 1967 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Route 25A, 1969 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Route 110A, 1969 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Route 110 - Jericho, 1966-1968 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Sagtikos Manor Historical Society, 1967 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Salesman Bill, 1969 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Sale of Meat, 1968 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Sales Tax, 1966-1967 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Sales Tax, 1969 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Sanitarians, 1968 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - School Aid, 1969 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - School Athletic Program Bill, 1969 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - School Board Teacher Relations Bill, 1967 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - School Bus Transportation, 1967 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - School Districts, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - School Lunch, 1968 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 36-37)
  - Senate Standing Committee on Taxation, 1968 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Senior Citizen, 1968 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Senior Citizen Tax Bill, 1969 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Sewage System, 1967 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Social Security, 1969 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Social Services, Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Social Services, 1969 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Social Services Law, 1968; Undated (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Social Welfare [1 of 2], 1966-1967 (Box 8 (1-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Social Welfare [2 of 2], 1967-1968 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Social Workers, 1968 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Southhold Signs, 1966; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - South Mall, 1969 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Speech, 1968; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Speech Material, 1968 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Speech Material, 1969 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - State Budget Cutback Letters and Telegrams, 1969 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9-10)
  - State Education Department File, 1968 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - State Liquor Authority, 1967 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - State Police, 1968 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - State Revenue, 1967-1968 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - State University, 1969 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Statistics, Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Statute of Limitations, Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Statute of Limitations Bill, 1967 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Steuben Society of America, 1968 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Striped Bass Game Fish Bill, 1969 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20-21)
  - Subsidies to Builders, Plumbers, 1966 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Suffolk County, 1969 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Suffolk County Hearing and Speech Center, 1967 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Suffolk County Organization for the Promotion of Education (SCOPE), 1969 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25-26)
  - Suffolk County Schools Listing, Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Suffolk County Water Authority, 1967 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Suffolk State School (Melville), 1966-1968 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Supreme Court Judges, 1968 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Syracuse University, 1969 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Tax Budget, 1968 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Taxation - General Information, 1965-1968 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Taxes, 1966-1968 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Taxes, 1968 (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 35-36)
  - Taxes, 1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Taylor Act, 1968 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Taylor Law, 1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Teacher Retirement, 1968 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 4-5)
  - Teacher Retirement, 1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Teacher Salary Bill, 1967 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Telephone, New York State, 1968 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - "The Thoroughbred Record and the Racing Calendar" (Publication), 1967 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Town Law, 1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Town of Islip, 1968 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Town of Islip, 1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Traffic Light, 1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Traffic Safety, 1968 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Transit, New York City, 1966 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority, 1967 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Tuition, 1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Unemployment Insurance Plan, 1968 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Utilities, 1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Utilities and Rules, 1967-1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Urban Development, 1968 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Veterans, 1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Veterinary, 1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Village of Port Jefferson, 1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Village Law, 1968 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Village of Patchogue, 1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Volunteer Firemen, 1968 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Volunteer Firemen, 1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Vocational Education, 1968 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Welfare, 1967-1968 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Welfare, 1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Wild River, 1968-1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Wiretap, 1969 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Working Notes on Highway Package, 1966-1968 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1968 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Wire Tapping, 1968 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Youth Programs, 1963-1966 (Box 10 (1-Subject Files), Folder 37)
- Bills, 1967-1968; 2; .65 cu. ft.
  Arranged chronologically by bill number.
  Series 2, Bills, features files for pertaining to each of the bills that Smith introduced in the State Senate 1968.
  - S. 262, Social Ser. Law, restrict assist. For persons not having state residence, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 38)
  - S. 377, Penal Law, forfeiture of vessel, veh., aircraft in trans. gambling devices, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 39)
  - S. 379, Education Law, approval of drainage for schools (new or add), 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 40)
  - S. 380, Education Law, School fire alarms, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 41)
  - S. 430, Education Law, levying tax non-prof. salaries, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 42)
  - S. 432, Highway Law, consultation Supt. Of public work and local governing bodies in planning State Highway proj., 1967-1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 43)
  - S. 433, Highway Law, designation of State highways in Suffolk, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 44)
  - S. 434, Real Prop. Tax Law, income of persons over 65, eligible for partial exemption, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 45)
  - S.884, Town Law-improve Dists., payments, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 46)
  - S. 1021, Navig. Law-outboard motors, sales, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 47)
  - S. 1179, Multi-Sponsored, Educ., educ. Dept. review board, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 48)
  - S. 1234, Soc. Services Laws-work relief assigns, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 49)
  - S. 1235, Soc. Services Law-priv. nursing homes, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 50)
  - S. 1360, Penal Law-gambling devices seizures, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 51)
  - S. 1378, Navig. Law-water skiing, regulations, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 52)
  - S. 1380, Education Law - NYC, School construction, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 53)
  - S. 1381, Election Law - absentee voting, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 54)
  - S. 1489, Gen. Municipal Law - officers, fin. Interest, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 55)
  - S. 1505, An act in relation to assess and coll. Of taxes in Suffolk Co., 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 56)
  - S. 1566, Tax Law - local reality transfer taxes, 1967-1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 57)
  - S. 1598, Penal Law - oper. And main. Radio receiving sets - regulations, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 58)
  - S. 1758, Retire. and Soc. Security Law - final salary of policemen and firemen, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 59)
  - S. 1759, Public off. Law - leave of absence for vet., 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 60)
  - S. 1859, Multi- Sponsored, Educ., state aid apportionment, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 61)
  - S. 1860, Multi- Sponsored, Educ., state aid apportionment, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 62)
  - S. 1890, Civil Serv. - veterans/ preference, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 63)
  - S. 2139, Banking Law - aggregate unpaid loans, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 64)
  - S. 2203, Banking Law - Saving bks., investments, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 65)
  - S. 2220, Banking Law - Personal Loan departments, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 66)
  - S. 2308, Penal Law - physical force in defense, 1968 (Box 10 (2-Bills), Folder 67)
  - S. 2309, Public Health Law- funeral students, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 1)
  - S. 2364, Metro. Transport, auth. Reality taxes, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 2)
  - S. 2365, Retire. and Soc. Sec. Law - Suffolk Co., Sheriff. Retire, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 3)
  - S. 2366, Retire. SS, sheriffs, under-sheriffs, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 4)
  - S. 2367, Educ., schl. Construction actions, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 5)
  - S. 2512, Melville Vol. Firemen's Assn., 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 6)
  - S. 2527, Bank., office location changes, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 7)
  - S. 2528, Savings., loan assns., home mtg. loans., 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 8)
  - S. 2530, Suffolk Co., addl. County judge, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 9)
  - S. 2531, Suffolk Co., addl. Family ct. judge, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 10)
  - S. 2619, Judy., 10th dist., supr. Ct. judges, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 11)
  - S. 2894, Greenlawn Vol. Firemen's Assn., 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 12)
  - S. 2953, Education Law- landscape architecture, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 13)
  - S. 3261, Per. Prop. Law - home solicit, contracts, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 14)
  - S. 3346, Navig. Law - boat liveries, regulns, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 15)
  - S. 3347, Navig. Law - pleasure boats, markings, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 16)
  - S. 3348, Navig. Law - water skiers, regulns., 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 17)
  - S. 3350, Criminal Code - Suffolk Co., cert. loc. Police, powers, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 18)
  - S. 3429, State Park police, medical care, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 19)
  - S. 3430, dpts. Educ., County Library, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 20)
  - S. 3431, Educ., Practice of Pharmacy, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 21)
  - S. 3469, Bank., banks, net profits, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 22)
  - S. 3586, Navig. Boats, beaching, regulations, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 23)
  - S. 3633, Navig., boats, pollution controls, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 24)
  - S. 3634, Nassau co., drug addict boat drivers, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 25)
  - S. 3649, Multi-Sponsored, Elect., electors' certificates, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 26)
  - S. 3675, Deer Park Vol. Firemen's Assn., 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 27)
  - S. 3684, Educ., certain schl. Dist. Voters, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 28)
  - S. 3762, Suffolk Co. police, retirements, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 29)
  - S. 3763, Conserv., health insur. Plan, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 30)
  - S. 3765, Tax, sales, use tax collectors, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 31)
  - S. 3766, Tax, sales, use tax credits, refunds, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 32)
  - S. 3767, Tax, sales to veterinarians, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 33)
  - S. 4041, Conserv, timber harvesters, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 34)
  - S. 4578, Penal., bail jumping, define, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 35)
  - S. 4581, Penal, unlawful collect. Practice, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 36)
  - S. 4582, Penal, public lewdness, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 37)
  - S. 5506 Committee on Rules, Town of Babylon, 1968 (Box 11 (2-Bills), Folder 38)